budgetinternational.com 2018-10-08

# PRIVACY NOTICE

PRIVACY
NOTICE

                                                 Privacy Notice
                                       Notice Last Updated: May 2018
Welcome to the Privacy Notice of those Avis, Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent and France Cars companies
within the Avis Budget Group, Inc. that are located in the European Union (we refer to these companies as
"ABG," "we," "us," or "our" in this Privacy Notice). A full list of these companies and contact details is
included below: see Data Controllers and Contact Details by Country.
Please take the time to read this Privacy Notice as it is important for you to know how we collect and use
your personal information. By "personal information" we mean all information that relates to a living
individual and either identifies, or may be used to identify, that individual.
The nature of our business and our services to you may require us to share information with our
independent licensees. This Privacy Notice does not apply to those Avis, Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent
and France Cars locations that are owned and operated by an independent licensee not owned nor
controlled by ABG or any ABG affiliate or subsidiary. Click here to learn more about independent locations.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the use of your personal information by any independent
location, please contact us at DPO@abg.com.
ABG may change portions of this Privacy Notice from time to time, so be sure to check back. If we make a
change that significantly affects your rights or, to the extent we are permitted to do so, significantly changes
how we use your personal information, we will notify you by way of a prominent posting on our websites, e-
mail and/or postal mail prior to the change becoming effective.
Please select any of the following hyperlinks to learn about the ways we collect, use, share and disclose
personal information:
GETTING STARTED
RENTING A VEHICLE
VEHICLE DATA
PHOTOS & VIDEO
ONLINE DATA
ONLINE ADVERTISING
MARKETING
ANALYTICS
CHILDREN
INFORMATION SHARING
YOUR CHOICES
SAFEGUARDS
INFORMATION RETENTION
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
DATA CONTROLLERS AND CONTACT DETAILS BY COUNTRY
INDEPENDENT LOCATIONS
2

GETTING STARTED
ABG wants you to feel comfortable about giving us access to your personal information. Use this Privacy
Notice to find out what happens to your personal information when you interact with ABG and what choices
you have.
This Privacy Notice does not apply to our independent licensee locations. Please review the privacy notices
of our independent licensees for information on how they use personal information that you provide to them.
This Privacy Notice covers the personal information the ABG companies collect, use and disclose through
your use of our products and services either online or offline.
ABG needs to collect personal information from you to rent a vehicle or provide our other services. We
collect personal information when you give it to us, such as by telephone, fax, postal mail, email, at the
counter, upon completion of an application or enrollment form, joining our Avis Preferred loyalty scheme or
through your use of one of ABG's website or mobile Apps or the use of our products and services.
Please be aware that, in certain circumstances, where you do not provide personal information which is
required by us, we will not be able to provide the products and services under our contract with you or may
not be able to comply with a legal obligation on us. For example, when renting a vehicle with us we will
require information such as your name, address, payment information and driver's licence. If you fail to
provide this information to us we will be unable to rent a vehicle to you. You will be made aware if this
situation arises and what the consequences of not providing the personal information will be.
Sometimes, we will combine the personal information we receive from you with other information we
received from other sources so we can provide you a more customised and hassle-free experience. This
information may include your name, contact information, travel itinerary, booking request and other
information that is relevant to your booking. These third parties include:
     •   Travel agents or a third-party booking service that you used to make your reservation;
     •   Your employer or association if you are using a corporate / association account;
     •   Our licensees and our affiliates, in order to create a Wizard account or if you are making a booking
         in one location served by our affiliates or licensees for rental services in another location served by
         us; and
     •   Police and other law enforcement agencies if you are involved in an accident during your rental, or
         suffer any loss, damage or theft of the vehicle, or if you incur any speeding, parking, toll or other
         traffic-related fines or commit any traffic offences during your rental.
The purposes for which we use this information is set out in further detail in the rest of this Privacy Notice.
There are a number of bases in data protection law that permit Avis to use your personal information for
these purposes. These are: (1) that you have provided your consent to us using your personal information
for that purpose (e.g. where you have given us your consent to send you electronic marketing); (2) that we
need to use that personal information in order to fulfil our contract to provide products or services to you
(e.g. using your information for vehicle rentals or join our loyalty programme, “Avis Preferred”); (3) that the
processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests, provided we have balanced these
3

against your rights and interests; and (4) where we need to comply with a legal obligation (e.g. responding
to government or law enforcement information requests).
These legitimate interests are: (a) to ensure effective administration and management of your relationship
with us, including any rentals with us; (b) to understand how our customers use our services and to manage
our vehicle fleet; (c) to carry out research and analysis on what services or products our customers want or
how they would like us to improve our services and products; (d) to understand how our customers use our
websites and Apps and identify any issues in how the websites and Apps are used and how we can improve
the customers usage experience; (e) to tell our customers about the various products and services we can
offer; (f) understand and respond to customer feedback; (g) to better tailor and personalise the promotions
and benefits that we offer to our customers; (h) to prevent, detect, or investigate unauthorised use of our
vehicles and systems and ensure we comply with law and our policies; and (i) manage any disputes and
accidents and take legal or other professional advice.
We will collect technical information about your devices when you use our website and App where
permitted. To learn about our online data collection, go to the Online Data section.
RENTING A VEHICLE
When you make a reservation, rent a vehicle or join one of our programs such as a corporate programme
or our Avis Preferred loyalty scheme, we collect information to provide you with our great services (for
example, renting a vehicle, including performing the vehicle rental contract as set out in our General
Conditions of Rental, Location Specific Conditions and Rental Agreement, providing any requested optional
extras, taking payment, pre-authorisations and security deposits and providing discounts and offers or other
benefits) and for our legitimate business interests (for example research and development of new products
and services, undertaking fraud and security checks and enforcing our legal rights). The information we
collect includes:
•      name;
•      email address (if you are booking online or wish to receive e-receipts);
•      home address (for license validation and billing);
•      employer details and business address (if you are a member of a corporate program);
•      telephone numbers at which we can reach you;
•      date of birth (for license validation and legal requirements);
•      gender (for license validation);
•      payment information such as your credit or debit card details (security code is obtained for transaction
       only – we do not keep it);
•      tax number (if specifically requested);
•      information from driver's licence and/or other government issued identification, including if you are
       an additional driver for the specific rental (for license validation and legal requirements);
•      information from another form of identification documentation such as passport or national identity
       card if your driver's licence does not include a photo or is not recognisable as you and/or proof of
       address such as a utility bill (for security and anti-fraud purposes). The information we collect and
       retain will only include your photo ID where you are informed of this;
•      special discount codes, partner member numbers, association memberships, corporate rewards
       programs (if you request discounts, special privileges and points programs);
4

•      special requests and preferences, including:
       o    your preferences regarding optional extras such as damage waivers and other protections;
       o    where a delivery or collection service is available, the address where we will drop off or pick-up
            the vehicle and any optional extras you requested; and
•      other information that may be required to rent you a vehicle and/or provide you with services.
Some vehicles come equipped with a global positioning system (GPS) or similar type tracking device that
may also collect information about the vehicle. To learn about vehicle data we collect, scroll down to read
about Vehicle Data.
If you have an accident, or suffer any loss, theft or damage to the vehicle during your rental or suffer any
mechanical failure, we will collect information regarding such incident including your report of the incident
and any police or other third party report including details of those involved, together with the nature of any
personal injuries and/or damage to the vehicle and optional extras. We will use this information to perform
our contract with you (for example, the vehicle rental agreement and/or the terms of any optional extra like
insurance); for our legitimate business interests (for example, in recovering the costs of any loss or damage
caused to the vehicle); for complying with any legal obligation on us (for example, making any required
notification of the incident to appropriate authorities); and establishing, exercising or defending legal claims
arising as a result of such incident.
During your rental we will collect where and when you rented the vehicle, where and when you returned
the vehicle, insurance preferences, fuel consumption, mileage, accident history and other information
related to the vehicle and your use of it. This information is required in order to provide you with the services
you requested under the rental contract or for our legitimate business interests (for example to monitor the
usage of our vehicle fleet).
In addition to the purposes listed above, we use this information to better understand our customers and
provide you with relevant offers.
We will also collect information about any speeding, parking, toll or other traffic-related fines that you incur
or any traffic offences that you commit during your rental where these are provided to us by any law
enforcement agency. We will use this information to deal with such fine or offence in accordance with the
terms of your vehicle rental agreement with us.
Where you inform us that you have a medical disability that requires an adapted vehicle or other driver aid
we will use that information in order to provide you with the service you requested and where you have
given your explicit consent to us using that information.
When you call us (from any phone), we may record or monitor the call for quality control, training or similar
purposes.
When you purchase a gift certificate or voucher, we collect the name and mailing address of the gift recipient
in order to fulfill your order. We will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided.
If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like
to request that it be removed from our database, please contact our customer service at the details set out
in the Data Controllers and Contact Details by Country section below.
5

AVIS PREFERRED
If you decide to join our Avis Preferred loyalty programme we will collect and retain your name, contact
details, drivers licence details, and date of birth to create an Avis Preferred account for you in accordance
with the terms and conditions of the Avis Preferred programme,
We will use this information, along with information relating to your historic and future rentals, to allow you
to take the benefits of membership of the Avis Preferred programme, including fast-track service at our
rental counters, the ability to self-service elements of the rental through our App, and to provide you with
further benefits to which you are entitled under the programme such as free upgrades and free rentals.
We also use this information to tailor the communications we may send to you and/or the promotions we
may offer to you as a member of Avis Preferred from time to time.
We will also use this information for our internal analysis of how our customers use our services and to
improve how we provide our services.
INSURANCE PRODUCTS
If you have requested any of the insurance products that we offer during your rental, such as Personal
Accident Insurance or Super Personal Accident Insurance, we will pass your personal information to the
insurer that is underwriting that product in connection with you entering into a contract with that insurer for
that product. The name of the insurer will be made available to you when you are requesting the relevant
product.
In the event that you make any claim under one of these insurance products, your personal information
relating to the claim will be provided to the insurer and any appointed claims handler. We do this to fulfil
the terms of our agreement with you and to establish, exercise or defend any associated legal claims.
The use of your personal information by that insurer will be subject to the terms of that insurer's privacy
notice.
VEHICLE DATA
Some vehicles you rent from ABG have been manufactured or equipped with on-board devices so as to be
connected to the internet (connected car) which allow us to send commands to and receive certain
information from the vehicle, including geolocation data from a global positioning system (GPS). If you rent
a connected car from us your personal information will be processed in accordance with this Notice and the
Connected Cars Privacy Addendum included in the General Conditions of Rental (or such other notice
regarding connected cars as we may provide to you in the future).
PHOTOS & VIDEO
Where indicated by signage at the relevant location, ABG rental locations are also equipped with video
security surveillance systems as well as cameras that record as our vehicles depart/enter our lots.
ONLINE DATA
When you download, visit and use our websites and/or Apps, ABG automatically collects technical
information. This section tells you more about what technical information we collect and why we collect it.
6

IP Addresses & other information collected automatically: We may collect your IP address when you visit
our websites to help us diagnose problems with our main computers, for system administration, to report
aggregated information to our business partners, and to audit the use of our website. We do not normally
link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. In select circumstances, we may use IP addresses to
help us identify you when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Website Terms and
Conditions or to protect our service, site, users or others. We may also collect your browser type, Internet
Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.),
operating system, date/time stamp, and/ or clickstream data to analyse trends in the aggregate and
administer the site.
Session Replay: When you visit our website, we will sometimes also record information about your
browsing session on the site, including which pages you visited and any forms on the website that you
completed. We review this information to identify any technical issues in the operation of our sties and to
improve the user interface our sites. We use a third party to help us with this service and this information
will be passed to that third party for this purpose but this information is not disclosed to any other third party.
Cookies & other similar technologies: Please refer to our Cookies                            Policy  located     at
https://www.avis.co.uk/about-avis/cookie-policy for details of how we use cookies.
Mobile Analytics: When you download and use our Avis, Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent and France Cars
Car Rental Apps, we use mobile analytics software to help us better understand the functionality of our App
on your mobile device. Our analytics may record how often you use the App, how you use the App,
aggregated usage, performance data and where you downloaded the App from. To read more about how
we use information for research please see the Analytics section.
Mobile GPS and Push Notifications: If you let us, when you use our Avis, Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent
and France Cars Car Rental Apps we may collect location markers using the GPS in your device. Knowing
approximately where you are helps the App provide you better service, such as finding the nearest Avis,
Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent and France Cars rental location near you. This also helps us send you
push notifications or other communications based on your location (for example, nearby special offers) and
for providing certain services such as arrival and return notifications, providing information about vehicle
location, available upgrades, etc. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the
purpose of providing you our services. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect
certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information. If you
change your mind about sharing your location or receiving push notifications from the App, adjust the
settings of your mobile device to turn off transmission of geolocation data or to stop transmission of push
notifications at any time. Just remember if you do turn these features off, you will not receive information
tailored to your location or special locations-based offers.
ONLINE ADVERTISING
ABG uses third-parties to provide online or electronic ads on our behalf. These third parties use data about
your visits to our websites and Apps usage to send you customised ads that may be of interest to you. This
information is collected using cookies, scripts, pixel tags, etags, web beacons and other similar technologies
by ABG and our third-party advertising partners in accordance with our Cookie Policy.
7

MARKETING
ABG may share personal information with third parties (as detailed in the Information Sharing section) to
help us with our marketing and promotional projects, such as managing our social media pages, running
contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, or sending marketing communications.
We will only use your personal information to send you marketing where you have given us your consent
to receive marketing or we are otherwise permitted by applicable law to do so. This marketing will be sent
to you either electronically or to your postal address.
Don't want to receive promotional and marketing post, emails and text messages from ABG and our
partners? No problem! You can withdraw your consent to direct marketing or tell us you do not want to
receive such marketing at any time. See the Your Choices section to find out how.
ANALYTICS
We use analytic software, such as Adobe Analytics, Google Analytics and others, to help us to better
understand the functionality of our software on our websites and Apps on your device. These software tools
record technical information including about your device together with usage information such as how often
you use our website or App, which features you use or don't use in the website App or which pages you
visit on the website, aggregated usage, performance data, where the App was downloaded from and
information about your visit to the site, including details of some of the URL clickstream to, through and
from our website. Further information about these tools is set out in our Cookie Policy.
Want to learn about all what happens when you visit our websites or use our Apps? Learn more under the
Online Data section.
CHILDREN
ABG's websites, Apps and services are not for children under the age of 16. This includes any links to other
websites that we provide for your convenience. We don't knowingly collect personal information from
children for any reason. If you think ABG has received personal information of your child or another minor,
please contact our Data Protection Officer at the address set out in the Data Controllers and Contact Details
by Country section.
INFORMATION SHARING
ABG may use and share your personal information and vehicle data to affiliated and non-affiliated
organisations as follows:
  Third party recipient                 Purpose of disclosure                  Legal Basis for Processing
  Independent        licensees       /   •      Make and confirm your rental     •      Performance        of
  franchisees      and       network            reservation;                            Contract;
  providers in order to perform our       •     Provide our rewards program      •      Legitimate
  contract with you and to                      and update partner points               Interests;
  understand how you use our                    and rewards;
                                                                                 •      Legal obligation; or
8

  services and to improve our        • Connect with your corporate
                                                                         • Consent.
  business                             and commercial accounts;
                                     • Assist      with      navigation
                                       assistance       or     itinerary
                                       planning;
                                     • Provide customer assistance;
                                     • Resolve toll, traffic or parking
                                       violations;
                                     • Processing       any       claims
                                       relating to accidents and/or
                                       injuries;
                                     • Providing              roadside
                                       assistance services;
                                     • To protect or defend the rights
                                       or well-being of us, our
                                       employees, customers or
                                       others;
                                     • Verify safe driver criteria for
                                       qualified drivers.
  Travel agents in order to perform  • Make and confirm your rental      • Performance  of
  our contract with you when you       reservation;                        Contract; or
  use a travel agent and to          • Process       payments        and • Legitimate
  understand how you use our           refunds;                            Interests.
  services and to improve our
                                     • Assist      with      navigation
  business
                                       assistance       or     itinerary
                                       planning;
                                     • Provide customer assistance;
                                     • Providing              roadside
                                       assistance services;
                                     • To protect or defend the rights
                                       or well-being of us, our
                                       employees, customers or
                                       others.
  Your employer or organisation in   • Verify drivers licenses or        • Performance  of
  order to provide you with benefits   other               government      Contract; or
  of a corporate or association        identification.
                                                                         • Legitimate
  program and to understand how      • Verify eligibility to         use   interests.
  you use our services and to          designated account            and
  improve our business                 discount codes;
9

                                      •     Connect with your corporate
                                            and commercial accounts.
 Brokers in order to perform our      •     Make and confirm your rental    • Legitimate
 contract with you when you book            reservation;                      Interests.
 a rental through their service and   •     Process      payments      and
 to protect our business from fraud         refunds;
 and bad debts
                                      •     Provide customer assistance;
                                      •     Handle debt collection;
                                      •     Fraud check.
 Booking engines in order to          •     Make and confirm your rental    • Performance  of
 perform our contract with you              reservation.                      Contract; or
 when you use a booking engine        •     Verify eligibility to       use • Legitimate
 and to understand how you use              designated account         and    Interests.
 our services and to improve our            discount codes;
 business
                                      •     Process      payments      and
                                            refunds;
                                      •     To protect or defend the rights
                                            or well-being of us, our
                                            employees, customers or
                                            others.
 Credit card issuers in order to      •     Process      payments      and  • Performance  of
 obtain payment from you                    refunds;                          Contract; or
                                      •     Fraud check;                    • Legitimate
                                      •     Handle debt collection.           Interests.
 Corporate account manager in       If you are renting with a corporate,    • Performance  of
 order to provide you with benefits membership       or    other    similar   Contract; or
 of a corporate or association      commercial entity account, we may       • Legitimate
 program and to understand how      share personal information with the       interests.
 you use our services and to        organisation that manages the
 improve our business               account for their own purposes. We
                                    recommend you review their privacy
                                    policy to learn more about their
                                    privacy practices.
 Marketing agent in order to          •     Provide our rewards program     • Performance  of
 provide you with benefits of a             and update partner points         Contract; or
 corporate or association program           and rewards;                    • Legitimate
 and to understand how you use        •     To protect or defend the rights   Interests.
 our services and to improve our            or well-being of us, our
 business                                   employees, customers or
                                            others.
10

  IT service providers including IT      •    Support our IT systems and          •     Legitimate
  platform providers and website              infrastructure;                           interests.
  analytics service providers in         •    Provide             maintenance
  order to in order to perform our            services for our IT systems
  contract with you and to                    and infrastructure;
  understand how you use our             •    Provision of data hosting and
  services and to improve our
                                              other      data       processing
  business                                    services;
                                         •    Provide analytics services
                                              relating to your use of our
                                              website to identify any
                                              technical or user interface
                                              issues and/or improvements
                                              in connection with the website
  Government, regulatory and law         •    To verify your driver's license     •     Legal requirement;
  enforcement agencies in order to            and ensure you meet our safe              or
  meet our legal obligations                  driver criteria;
                                                                                  •     Legitimate
                                         •    As requested by these
                                                                                        interests.
                                              agencies if the disclosure is
                                              required or permitted by law;
                                         •    To take action regarding
                                              illegal     activities,    traffic
                                              offences or violations of terms
                                              of service;
                                         •    If we have a good faith belief
                                              that there is an emergency
                                              that poses a threat to the
                                              safety of you or another
                                              person; and
                                         •    As otherwise required or
                                              permitted by law.
  Insurance companies and claims         •    Provide and service the             •     Performance       of
  handlers in respect of any                  insurance product you have                contract; or
  insurance product you purchase              requested;
                                                                                  •     Legitimate
  in connection with your rental
                                         •    Manage any claims that may                interests.
                                              be made under the relevant
                                              insurance policy
We may also transfer or assign your personal information to third parties as a result of, or in connection
with a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of assets, bankruptcy, reorganisation, or
liquidation. Or if we are involved in defending a legal claim, information about you that is relevant to such
claim may be disclosed to third parties as a result of, or in connection with, associated legal proceedings.
We may, in accordance with the Marketing section, share your information with business and promotional
partners (where you have provided your consent to such information sharing) in order to send you
11

information about products and services you may like. If you decide you no longer want to receive such
promotional and marketing messages, please read the Your Choices section to find out how you can opt-
out.
YOUR CHOICES
If you want to opt out of receiving promotional and marketing emails, text messages, post and other forms
of communications from ABG or our promotional partners in relation to which you might receive in
accordance with the Marketing section, you can best opt out by using one of the following ways:
              •   Log into your account and update your profile.
              •   Click "unsubscribe" at the bottom of an email we sent you.
              •   Go to our Data Controllers and Contact Details by Country section to email the customer
                  service representative suited for you.
To stop receiving promotional text messages:
              •   For our Avis customers text the word "STOP" to 48400; and
              •   For our Budget customers text the word "STOP" to 36300.
              •   For our Maggiore Rent customers text the word “STOP” to 48400.
If you do opt out of receiving promotional and marketing messages, we can still contact you regarding our
business relationship with you, such as account status and activity updates, survey requests in respect of
products and services we have provided to you after you rent from us, reservation confirmations or respond
to your inquiries or complaints, and similar communications.
Want to close your account, stop doing business with ABG, or otherwise opt out of ABG collecting, using
or disclosing your personal information? We will be sorry to see you go. Please contact our customer service
representatives in accordance with the Data Controllers and Contact Details by Country section.
Please also see your rights set out in Your Privacy Rights section.
SAFEGUARDS
The security of your personal information is important to us. We take reasonable steps to make sure your
information is protected from unauthorised use, access, disclosure, alteration, destruction or loss. For
financial or payment information, we use firewalls and Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption. We take
security extremely seriously but as no system is 100% secure, we can't completely guarantee the protection
of your personal information, any more than any other organisation can.
We do not ask for financial or payment information, such as your credit card number, passcode, account
number or pin number, in an e-mail, text or any other communication that we send to you. Please always
check that any website on which you are asked for financial or payment information in relation to our rentals
or services is operated by ABG or its affiliates. If you do receive a suspicious request, do not provide your
information and report it by contacting one our customer service representatives as set out in the Data
Controllers and Contact Details by Country section.
12

You are responsible for keeping your account passcode, membership numbers and pin numbers safe and
secure. Don't share those with anyone. If there is an unauthorised use or any other breach of security
involving your information, you must notify us at the customer service contact information below as soon
as possible.
INFORMATION RETENTION
ABG keeps your personal information for no longer than is reasonably necessary or required by law. How
long we keep it depends very much on the type of information and purpose.
The criteria we use to determine the retention period for certain categories of data is as follows
    •    the length of time that you are a member of Avis Preferred or any other loyalty scheme that we
         operate or a member of any corporate programme;
    •    how frequently you rent with us or when you most recent rental occurred;
    •    whether there are contractual or legal obligations that exist that require us to retain the data for
         period of time;
    •    whether there is any ongoing legal claim that relates to any rental you have made with us, or that
         is otherwise related to your relationship with us;
    •    whether any applicable law, statute, or regulation allows for a specific retention period;
    •    whether the personal information is considered to be a special category of personal information, in
         which case a shorter retention period generally would be applied; and
    •    what the expectation for retention was at the time the data was provided to us.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
Rentals
As we offer the ability to rent vehicles and benefit from our services in many locations globally, we will
transfer your personal information to our affiliates, independent licensees and travel agents in these
locations for the purposes of fulfilling your rental request and/or entering into a rental agreement. The exact
location of where your personal data will be transferred depends on the location of your rental. A list of
these locations on our website at https://www.avis.co.uk/drive-avis/car-hire-locations.
Many of the countries to which your personal information may be transferred for these purposes that are
located outside the EU do not benefit from an adequacy decision issued by the EU Commission regarding
protection afforded to personal information in that country. Details of these specific countries can be found
here:            https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-
protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en.
These transfers are made either as they are necessary for the performance of a contract to which you will
be a party, or for pre-contractual measures. Alternatively, adequacy of data protection is ensured by
standard data protection clauses that we have in place with the relevant recipient. A copy of these standard
data protection clauses may be requested via our Data Protection Officer at the address set out in the Data
Controllers and Contact Details.
13

Business operations
In addition, the information we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored by, IT vendors who
operate on our behalf. In particular, these include our booking engine hosting provider that is located in the
United States. We also transfer information to a number of providers of business application – such as
CRM and marketing applications – as well marketing service providers. These providers are primarily
located in the United States.
The United States does not benefit from a decision issued by the EU Commission regarding protection
afforded to personal information. Adequacy of data protection is instead ensured by standard data
protection clauses we have in place with that third party. A copy may be requested via our Data Protection
Officer at the address set out in the Data Controllers and Contact Details.
Given the global nature of our business, we also transfer information within the group companies of Avis
Budget Group, Inc as for certain activities the group uses shared IT functions. Transfers from within the
European Union for these purposes are primarily made to the United States, although transfers may be
made to other countries as well. The United States and many of the other countries located outside the
European Union do not benefit from an adequacy decision issued by the EU Commission regarding
protection afforded to personal information in that country. Adequacy of data protection is instead ensured
by standard data protection clauses we have in place with the recipient. A copy may be requested via our
Data Protection Officer at the address set out in the Data Controllers and Contact Details.
YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
You may have – in accordance with applicable data protection laws – the following rights when it comes to
our handling of your personal information:
    •    Right of access – you may have the right to request a copy of the personal information we have
         about you and to request supporting information explaining how the personal information is used.
    •    Right of rectification – you may have the right to request that we rectify inaccurate personal
         information about you.
    •    Right of erasure – you may have the right to request that we erase personal information about
         you.
    •    Right to restrict processing – in some situations, you may have the right to request that we do
         not use the personal information you have provided (e.g. if you believe it to be inaccurate).
    •    Right to data portability – you may have the right to receive certain of your personal information
         in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit such information to
         another controller.
    •    Right to withdraw consent – where we process your personal information based on consent
         (including direct marketing consents), you have the right to withdraw consent at any time. However,
         this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
         Furthermore, even in case of a withdrawal we may continue to use your personal information as
         permitted or required by law.
14

Right to object: In addition, where we are processing your personal information based on a legitimate
interest (or those of a third party) you may challenge this. However, we may be entitled to continue
processing your information based on our legitimate interests or where this is relevant to legal claims.
You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing
purposes.
[In addition, if specifically provided for under your local law, you will have a right to define post-mortem
guidelines – meaning you may define guidelines regarding the storage, erasure and disclosure of your
personal data after your death.]
Please get in touch with our Data Protection Officer at the address set out in the Data Controllers and
Contact Details by Country section if you would like to exercise any of these rights or in case you should
have any concerns about how we process your personal information. You are also free to lodge complaint
with the supervisory authority, should you feel that we process your personal information in a way that is
against applicable law.
DATA CONTROLLERS AND CONTACT DETAILS BY COUNTRY
If you are making a rental or visiting a local country version of our websites or mobile sites in the following
countries, the data controller is listed in the table below.
You can also contact our Data Protection Officer in respect of any issues or questions you have regarding
our processing of your personal information. They act as the Data Protection Officer in respect of all of the
data controllers listed below and can be contacted at:
Email: dpo@abg.com
Postal Address: Data Privacy Officer, Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell, Berkshire, RG12 2EW,
United Kingdom
Telephone: +44 (0)1344 426644
  Country                 Data Controller                        Contact Information
  United Kingdom          Avis Budget UK Limited                 Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                                                                 Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
  United Kingdom          ACL Hire Limited                       Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                                                                 Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
  United Kingdom          Avis Budget EMEA Limited               Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                                                                 Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
  United Kingdom          Avis Budget Services Limited           Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                                                                 Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
15

 United Kingdom Avis Europe Risk Management       Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                Limited                           Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
 United Kingdom Zodiac Europe Limited             Avis Budget House, Park Road, Bracknell,
                                                  Berkshire, United Kingdom, RG12 2EW
 Sweden         Sweden Rent A Car AB              P.O. Box 6050, 171 06, Solna, Sweden
 Denmark        Avis Budget Denmark A/S           Roskildevej 14, DK-2620 Albertslund, Denmark
 Norway         RAC Norway AS                     Drengsrudbekken 12, Oslo, Asker, 1383,
                                                  Norway
 Italy          Avis Budget Italia SpA            Viale Carmelo Bene n° 70, 00139 Roma
 Italy          Bell’Aria S.p.A                   Viale Carmelo Bene n° 70, 00139 Roma
 Italy          Zodiac Italy Spa                  Viale Carmelo Bene n° 70, 00139 Roma
 Portugal       Sovial – Sociedade de Viaturas de Rua Professor Fernando da Fonseca, Edifício
                Aluguer, Lda.                     Visconde Alvalade, 6º piso, 1600-616 Lisboa,
                                                  Portugal
 Portugal       Sovialma – Sociedade de Viaturas  Rua Professor Fernando da Fonseca, Edifício
                de Aluguer, Lda.                  Visconde Alvalade, 6º piso, 1600-616 Lisboa,
                                                  Portugal
 France         Avis Location de Voitures         1, rue du Général Leclerc, 92800 Puteaux
 France         Milton Location de Voitures       1, rue du Général Leclerc, 92800 Puteaux
 France         AAA France Cars                   10 rue de Luyot, 59 113 Secli
 Belgium        Avis Belgium                      Kouterveldstraat 14, 1831 Diegem
 Luxembourg     Avis Location de Voitures SARL    Aeroport de Findel, L-1110 Findel
16

  Netherlands           Avis Budget Autoverhuur              Louis Armstrongweg 4, 1311 RK Almere
  Hungary               Avis Budget Group         Business   Kassak Lajos u. 19-25, 1134 Budapest,
                        Support Centre Kft                   Hungary
  Spain                 Avis Budget Group Contact Centre     World Trade Centre, Edificio Norte 5a Planta,
                        EMEA SA                              Moll de Barcelona s/n, 08039 Barcelona, Spain
  Spain                 Avis Alquile Un Coche S.A.           Avenida de Manoteras, nº 32, Edificio C, 28050
                                                             Madrid, Spain
  Germany               Avis Autovermietung Gesellschaft     Laaer Berg Strasse 43, 1100 Vienna, Austria
                        mbH
  Germany               Avis Autovermietung Gesellschaft     Zimmersmuehlenweg 21, 61437 Oberursel/Ts.,
                        GmbH & Co.KG                         Germany
  Switzerland           Avis Budget Autovemietung AG         Hofwsenstrasse         36, 8153      Rumlang,
                                                             Switzerland
  Switzerland           Garep AG                             Hofwsenstrasse         36, 8153      Rumlang,
                                                             Switzerland
  Poland                Jupol-Car Sp. Z.o.o.                 Lopuszanska 12A, 02-220, Warsaw, Poland
                        Avis Autovermietung Gesellschaft     Laaer Berg Straße 43, 1100 Vienna, Austria
  Austria
                        mbH
  Czech Republic        Avis Autovermietung GmbH             Organizacni slozka, Klimentska 46, Praha 1,
                                                             110 02, Ceská republika
INDEPENDENT LOCATIONS
Did you know that many Avis, Budget, Payless, Maggiore Rent and France Cars locations are
independently owned and operated? Each of these locations collects, uses and discloses personal
information for its own purposes. ABG does not control the independent licensee's or franchisee's use of
this personal information. Please ask to review the privacy notice for that location.
When you are dealing with an independent location, the licensee or franchisee is responsible for collecting
and processing payment and may engage in its own email campaigns and other forms of marketing to you.
ABG is not responsible for the compliance of the independent location with privacy laws. However, if you
believe the independent location is violating privacy laws, you may report this to ABG’s Data Protection
Officer at dpo@abg.com.
17

KEY CONTACTS
Want to talk to us? Check the list below to find out the best way to reach us. When you contact us, we may
take steps to verify your identity for security purposes.
                     I want to…                                         How to reach us
  •  Customer Service Avis and Budget                  Please check the website for your country for contact
                                                       details.
  •  Contact Maggiore Rent customer service             PHONE NUMBER +39 06 22456014
                                                        EMAIL ADDRESS reclami@maggiore.it
                                                       ADDRESS Viale Carmelo Bene, 70 - 00139 Roma
                                                       HOURS OF OPERATION Monday - Friday 09.00 am
                                                       - 13.00 pm.
18
